<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Google Ad Grants]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Google Ad Grants]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/google-ad-grants/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:49:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/google-ad-grants/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Google Dot Org - Local Giving: Special Programs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Google Dot Org - Local Giving: Special Programs</h1><p>We champion people and projects that are combatting the biggest human challenges of the 21st century. Learn more about a few spotlight programs we are proud to support. The recent Zika virus outbreak has caused concern around the world and last month, the World Health Organization (WHO) declared a Public Health Emergency.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c145fc50cb224853e47111aaf7efefc42abf5a48.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.google.org/special-programs/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4527e47c-3983-4699-8ed1-6a7cad099707</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:49:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Google Earth Outreach Visualise your cause and tell your story through Google’s mapping technologies.  Map out success for your organisation:  Create a customised map of your project sites in 10-minutes with Google Maps Create a narrative Google Earth movie and make it available on YouTube Host geospatial data online with Maps Engine & publish polished maps to the web with a Google Maps Engine grant* Collect data in the field with Android devices and Open Data Kit and map your data Online tutorials to help you get the most out of all available mapping tools *Google Maps Engine grants not currently available through Google for Non-Profits. Learn more at Google Earth Outreach.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/google-ad-grants/google-earth-outreach-visualise-your-cause-and-tell-your-sto/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9d00cff7-9207-4ca6-80e8-134b3ba2871b</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Google Apps for Non-Profits Reduce your IT costs and help staff and volunteers work together more effectively.  Get the job done with Google Apps for Non-Profits:  Get free access to the Google Apps suite including Gmail, Google Calendar and Google Drive Work better with colleagues through online collaboration Store documents in the cloud: 30 GB of storage across Gmail and Google Drive Stay connected from anywhere; securely access data anywhere 24/7 support; no hardware, no updates Google Apps for Non-Profits is free for all members of Google for Non-Profits</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/google-ad-grants/google-apps-for-non-profits-reduce-your-it-costs-and-help-st/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1ba32936-c3e6-412d-bcb7-f1a49335b732</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Programme Benefits  The Google for Non-profits Programme offers qualified organisations access to free versions of paid Google products and special features designed for non-profits. These tools can help non-profits find new donors and volunteers, work more efficiently and get supporters to take action.  Google for Non-profits members have access to the following products:   YouTube Non-profit Programme Premium branding capabilities on YouTube channels, increased uploading capacity, the ability to select customised thumbnail images and call-to-action overlay on your videos.  Google Ad Grants Free AdWords advertising to promote your website on Google.com through keyword targeting.  Google Apps for Non-profits Free Non-profit Edition of Google Apps.  Google Earth Outreach Grants Free licensing for Maps API Premier (US, England and Wales only).  One Today One Today is an app that brings together people and non-profits through the simple act of giving $1. (US only)</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/google-ad-grants/programme-benefits-the-google-for-non-profits-programme-off/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2e715390-dbbd-4c06-8639-9106c6017036</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>YouTube Non-Profit Program Tell the story of your organisation or cause through video on YouTube.  Lights. Camera. Action:  Free, enriched version of YouTube just for non-profits Drive viewers to action by placing a Call-to-Action overlay directly on your videos Customise the look & feel of your channel with your organisation’s logo and branding</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/google-ad-grants/youtube-non-profit-program-tell-the-story-of-your-organisati/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">336e9b72-7b9d-4a35-bc01-cde45994ba8a</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eligibility guidelines - Non-profits Help]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Eligibility guidelines - Non-profits Help</h1><p>Organisations that meet the following criteria are eligible to participate in the Google for Non-Profits programme: Based in one of the following countries: Australia Austria</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://support.google.com/nonprofits/answer/3215869?hl=en-AU&amp;ref_topic=3247288</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4026cdc1-53b2-40dc-a2c5-972ae6171424</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:47:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Google Dot Org - Global Giving: Global Impact Awards]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Google Dot Org - Global Giving: Global Impact Awards</h1><p>Nonprofits are changing the world and we're proud to support them. At Google, we drive impact by providing technology and grants, as well as opportunities for Googlers to give back.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/25e92ae540591910ee3d097009d11d1247122b4f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.google.org/global-giving/global-impact-awards/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ccd46919-7169-4629-8022-ae187ba43d26</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:46:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Google Dot Org - Global Giving: Seed Funding]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Google Dot Org - Global Giving: Seed Funding</h1><p>Seed funding is awarded to entrepreneurial nonprofits to bring innovative tech ideas to life and test their potential for scale. Human rights actors increasingly rely on diverse and new information streams, yet they have no sector-specific toolsets or protocols to help them to manage their information, share knowledge, and protect the data they collect.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/093cc41f89fa3ce1265941f966dcbf4b6839075e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.google.org/global-giving/seed-funding/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d6e968-cdbf-4d62-a054-9f5d79c15add</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:46:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[for Non-Profits]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>for Non-Profits</h1><p>As a member of Google for Non-Profits, you'll have access to premium Google products that are free for organisations like yours.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/26f985a0190273065e16650391feda43409a1601.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.google.com.au/intl/en/nonprofits/products/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">85d5e379-efd9-479d-9965-b44147aaf13e</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:45:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ladies Learning Code | Google for Nonprofits Case Study]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ladies Learning Code | Google for Nonprofits Case Study</h1><p>Ladies Learning Code works to empower everyone to feel comfortable learning beginner-friendly technical skills in a social, collaborative way. They have chapters across Canada, thriving youth programs called Girls Learning Code and Kids Learning Code and a permanent workshop space in Toronto.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/bfc59e4a1bca183c0a56b8a9d2605a13ec30eeaf.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.google.com.au/intl/en/nonprofits/casestudies/ladies-learning-code.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bcbec8ae-49d6-411c-b8e1-ea7ba0bac5a9</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:37:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>